ROS provides a powerful build and package management system called Catkin.
ROS には Catkin という強力なビルド・パッケージ管理システムが用意されています
Willow Garage, the early developers of ROS,
ROS の初期のデベロッパー Willow Garage が
named Catkin after the flowers on the willow trees surrounding their office.
オフィスを囲む柳の木の花にちなんで Catkin と名付けました
A Catkin workspace is essentially a directory where
Catkin ワークスペースは 本質的には Catkin パッケージが
Catkin packages are built, modified and installed.
構築 修正 およびインストールされるディレクトリです
Typically when you're developing a ROS based robot or project,
一般に ROS ベースのロボットまたはプロジェクトを開発するときには
you will be working out of a single workspace.
単独のワークスペースで作業することになります
This singular workspace will hold a wide variety of Catkin packages.
この単独のワークスペースは 多様な Catkin パッケージを持ちます
All ROS software components are organized into and distributed as Catkin packages.
すべての ROS ソフトウェアコンポーネントは Catkin パッケージとしてまとめられ配布されます
Similar to workspaces, Catkin packages are
ワークスペースと同様に Catkin パッケージはさまざまなリソース
nothing more than directories containing a variety of resources which,
を含むディレクトリにすぎません これらはまとめて考えられると
when considered together constitute some sort of useful module.
ある種の便利なモジュールを構成します
Catkin packages may contain source code for nodes,
Catkin パッケージには ノード用のソースコード 便利なスクリプト
useful scripts, configuration files and more.
コンフィギュレーションファイルなどを含めることができます
In the sections that follow,
この後のセクションでは
you will see how to create a Catkin workspace,
Catkin ワークスペースを作成し
add packages to it,
ワークスペースにパッケージを追加し
manage inner package dependencies,
パッケージ間の依存関係を管理する方法
and lastly, how to successfully compile everything.
そして最後にすべてを正常にコンパイルする方法を説明します